<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Last Quest Wiki</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Language</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="humanDescription">Born on a strange planet named \"Earth\", the Human is a very
                                    versatile and well rounded race. Capable of soloing and being a
                                    team player, the Human is recommended for new players.</string>

    <string name="elfDescription">  Elves are known across realms as being the most beautiful
                                    creatures in the universe. Elves have higher dexterity however
                                    have lower strength from the trait of flight rather than fight.</string>

    <string name="dwarfDescription">Dwarf\'s are not as beautiful as the Elf, therefore start with
                                    lower charisma, intelligence and wisdom. Spending a lifetime living
                                    in mountains and caves, the Dwarf is known to have super-human
                                    strength and can take a million and one attacks from a foe.</string>

    <string name="hobbitDescription">The Hobbit is a small creature that like to stay low to the ground
                                     and are known to have a strange affinity with rings. Hobbits have
                                     cat like reflexes and golem like stamina therefore start with more
                                     reflex and constitution however starting with lower strength.</string>

    <string name="archerDescription">The Archer prefers to stay in the back of their group to take out
                                     enemies from afar. They are skilled in stealth and assassinating.
                                     An Archer is recommended for skilled players that have been playing
                                     for a longer than average time.</string>

    <string name="barbarianDescription">Barbarians are blood thirsty maniacs that only want to kill their
                                        enemies. Barbarians can enter a frenzied rage giving them a boost
                                        to Strength, Constitution and Dexterity however it lowers their
                                        Wisdom and Intelligence.</string>

    <string name="fighterDescription">A Fighter is a more balanced Barbarian, they favour striking their
                                      opponents with skillful precise strikes rather than swinging an
                                      axe around. The Fighter can be built to withstand enormous amounts
                                      of damage, or to deal enormous amounts of damage.</string>

    <string name="wizardDescription">The Wizard is an arcane caster, on a select few are able to learn
                                     to spells a Wizard can cast, and even fewer are able to handle the power.
                                     A Wizard is not good as soloing but instead working with the party to
                                     disable foes and buff party members.</string>


    <string name="welcomeText">Welcome</string>

    <string name="introText">This app is a wiki app for the Last Quest MMORPG made by RPG Inc. Please
                             select an option from the menu to navigate through</string>

    <string name="copyrightText">&#169; RPG Inc.</string>
    <string name="playableRaces">Playable Races</string>
    <string name="playableClasses">Playable Classes</string>
    <string name="selectLanguageLbl">Select Language</string>
    <string name="baseTraitsLbl">Base Traits</string>
    <string name="humanLbl">Human</string>
    <string name="descriptionLbl">Description</string>
    <string name="baseStatsLbl">Base Stats</string>
    <string name="strengthLbl">Strength</string>
    <string name="dexterityLbl">Dexterity</string>
    <string name="constitutionLbl">Constitution</string>
    <string name="intelligenceLbl">Intelligence</string>
    <string name="wisdomLbl">Wisdom</string>
    <string name="charismaLbl">Charisma</string>
    <string name="barbarianLbl">Barbarian</string>
    <string name="archerLbl">Archer</string>
    <string name="hobbitLbl">Hobbit</string>
    <string name="wizardLbl">Wizard</string>
    <string name="elfLbl">Elf</string>
    <string name="fighterLbl">Fighter</string>
    <string name="dwarfLbl">Dwarf</string>
    <string name="soloAbilityLbl">Solo Ability</string>
    <string name="defenseRatingLbl">Defense Rating</string>
    <string name="damageRatingLbl">Damage Rating</string>
    <string name="notableTraitLbl">Notable Traits</string>
    <string name="averageLbl">Average</string>
    <string name="highLbl">High</string>
    <string name="rangerTraitsLbl">Stealth, Ranged Attack</string>
    <string name="veryHighLbl">Very High</string>
    <string name="barbarianNotableTraitsLbl">Rage, Damage</string>
    <string name="veryHighOrAverageLbl">Very High or Average</string>
    <string name="highOrLowLbl">High or Low</string>
    <string name="fighterNotableTraitsLbl">Defense, Damage</string>
    <string name="lowLbl">Low</string>
    <string name="wizardNotableTraitsLbl">Spell Casting</string>
</resources>
